Previously on "Transformers Prime"...
在上一集里
Why rule only one world when I can rule two?
既然我能统治两个世界…
Megatron has managed to accomplish the first phase of his cyberforming of Earth...
威震天已经完成了数字化地球的第一阶段
the construction of his fortress.
建造他的堡垒
In Jasper, Nevada?
在贾斯帕 内华达？
I don't get it. Why here?
我不明白 他们干嘛要建在这儿？
Because the Decepticons have discovered the location of our base.
因为霸天虎已经发现了我们基地的位置
Come, my armada, attack!
上吧 我的舰队！进攻！
The base is lost.
基地已经沦陷了
We must disperse to avoid capture.
我们只有分散开才能成功突围
Special Agent Fowler to Air Defense Command.
特工福勒呼叫防空指挥部
I need immediate combat support.
我需要紧急战斗支援
No.
不！
Leave no stone unturned.
进行地毯式搜索！
Master, look who we found,
主人 看看我们找到了什么
pulled from the wreckage of his ship...
从飞船残骸中抓到的雷霆救援队员
Wheeljack.
千斤顶
So, one survived.
这么说 有一个死里逃生了
Take our guest back to the citadel for questioning. Back to Darkmount.
把我们的“贵客”带回大本营候审 带他回黑山
This is the dawning of a new age, my liege...
新时代的序幕已经拉开 我的君王
the reign of Megatron.
威震天的王朝开始了
You do have a way with words, Starscream.
你很能说会道啊 红蜘蛛
Make haste and unearth the Autobot corpses.
快点
The forge of Solus Prime?!
卓天越之锤？
How is it that you have managed to materialize that
你们有本事找得到这个
yet not the remains of a single Autobot?!
却搜不出一具汽车人的残骸？！
Answer your Lord and master.
快回答主人的话
Where are their bodies?!
他们的尸体在哪里？！
You're hurt,
你伤得重吗？
but you probably look way worse than you feel.
但你看上去要比你的实际情况还要糟
No, don't move or talk.
不 别动也别说话
Just power down. Get your strength back.
保存力量 恢复体力
I got you covered.
我会保护你的
The Autobots clearly ground bridged from their base before it was destroyed.
显然汽车人在我们摧毁基地前就利用环陆桥逃走了
They could be anywhere.
他们现在可能在任何地方
We must initiate global surveillance, my Lord.
我们必须启用全球监控 我的陛下
Send search-and-destroy teams to every sector of this planet.
派遣清理小队 查遍地球的每个角落
Soundwave, monitor all Earth-based transmissions for any sign of Autobot communication...
声波 监控所有汽车人的信号传输
with each other or with their human counterparts.
或是与其人类盟友之间的通讯信号
Master...
主人…
Mm. Foolish humans.
愚蠢的人类…
I shall deploy the armada.
我去部署大军
That won't be necessary, Starscream,
没这个必要 红蜘蛛
not when we can engage our enemy with newfound might.
何不让敌人尝尝我们的新力量！
A new power dominates your world.
一个新政权统治了你们的世界
Any further attempts to attack me will be met with even greater force.
任何针对我的进一步挑衅行为 我都会加倍奉还！
Your leaders should be advised
你们的领导人最好明白
that my fusion cannons possess enough firepower to decimate any densely populated area of my choosing.
我的融合炮能轻易摧毁任意一个密集居民区
I would, in all likelihood, set sights on your nation's capital, for starters.
我十有八九 会先拿你们的首都开刀
Point taken. Now, what do you want from us?
明白了 你到底想要什么？
Nothing, Agent Fowler.
我什么都不要 福勒特工
The Decepticons mean no harm to humanity.
霸天虎对人类没有恶意
We merely desire a place to call home.
我们只是渴望能有个栖身之所
No offense, Megatron, but I'm having a tough time
威震天 我无意冒犯
swallowing all this...
但我很难相信你的话
Since you seem so bent on plastering humankind under molten steel.
因为你一心想把人类置于你的魔爪之下！
Agent Fowler... I admit that war brings out the worst in me,
福勒特工 我承认战争将我最坏的一面展露无遗
but the conflict with the Autobots is now over,
但我们与汽车人之间的战争已经就此了结
and our quarrel has never been with your kind.
而且我们与人类之间并无瓜葛
Now that the one, true enemy of the Decepticons is no more,
既然霸天虎的真正敌人已经不复存在
my only wish is to coexist on this planet with the human race, peacefully.
我唯一的愿望就是能在这个星球上与人类…和平共处
Together, Agent Fowler,
福勒特工 你我携手
I believe that you and I can make that dream a reality.
这梦想定能成真
You, too, have a way with words, master.
您也蛮会忽悠的啊 主人
I almost believed you myself.
连我都差点儿相信您了
Earth is our planet now, Starscream,
地球现在归我们了 红蜘蛛
and we shall finish what we started.
是时候收锣罢鼓了
Humankind has no idea
人类绝对想不到在谎言的背后…
what lies ahead for them.
等待他们的将是什么
Yes, General Bryce.
是的 布莱斯将军
Special containment protocol G-1000 has been executed as planned.
特别应急方案G-1000已照计划执行
Evacuation of Jasper, Nevada, was 100% successful.
内华达贾斯帕的疏散行动非常成功
As far as its citizens or the media are concerned, the threat was a meteor shower
对市民和媒体公布的说辞 是流星雨导致的灾难
and the town is to remain quarantined until the resulting radiation levels can be dissipated.
在其造成的辐射消退前 城镇将持续封锁…
Sir, any form of retaliation would be too risky.
长官 任何形式的反击都过于冒险了！
I just need more time.
我需要更多的时间！
Yes, I understand.
好 我明白了…
Agent Fowler,
福勒探员
those medical supplies still haven't arrived. We have wounded men who need...
那些医疗物资仍然没有到位 我们有伤员急需…
doing the best I can, nurse Darby.
我已经竭尽全力了 达比护士
I've been a little busy juggling a bunch of nuke-happy generals who don't seem to care if they blow Nevada sky-high
我一直忙于应付那群刚上任 一心只想把事闹大的将军们
and a Decepticon warlord who wants to make nice
还有那个假意向我们示好的霸天虎暴君
now that the Autobots are in the scrapyard...
只因为汽车人都进了废铁场
Megatron's opinion, not mine.
当然那是威震天的想法 不是我的
He's feeding me a load of horse pucky, trying to crush our spirit.
他对我说了一堆屁话 妄图击垮我们的意志
Still no word from anyone?
还是没有任何人的消息？
Listen,
听我说
no contact only tells me that the main comm link went down when the base was pounded into pancake batter.
没有消息只能表示核心通讯器在基地被炸平时毁坏了
But if I could just call Jack...
但是如果我给杰克打个电话…
You know it's too risky. So do the bots.
你知道这样做有多危险 汽车人也一样
The Cons could trace any cellphone signal.
虎子们可以监测任何手机信号
Then take me home.
那就带我回家
If Jack can't call, that's where he'll look for me.
如果杰克联系不上我 他一定会去那里找我
Jasper's under complete comm lockdown. Nobody's getting back in there.
贾斯帕已经被虎子彻底封锁 谁都回不去了
The only ones who can fix this mess are Prime and his bots.
只有擎天柱还有他的汽车人能解决这场危机
I'm sure they're out there
我敢肯定他们就在某处
keeping a low profile.
低调行事
They got to be.
一定是这样的！
Scanning.
扫描中…
Negative. No Autobot recognition.
非预期结果…无汽车人身份识别
Clear.
走了！
Too close. But your paint job did the trick.
好险 不过你的喷漆蒙混过关了！
The comm sub link is still down.
看来子通讯链还没有恢复
Bee,
小蜂
I realize Optimus sent us all to different locations to make us harder for the Cons to find,
我明白擎天柱为避免虎子抓到我们 将我们分别传送到不同地点
but if we don't know where in the world anyone else went,
但如果我们不知道其他人的位置
how are we gonna find them?
该怎么找到他们呢？！
Right. Just keep heading toward Jasper...
你说得对 我们只能继续向贾斯帕前进
toward Megatron's giant fortress.
前往威震天巨大的堡垒
I never knew there were so many rockies.
从没想到路会这么难走
Miko!
神子！
No cellphone! You know the rules.
不许用手机 你知道规矩的！
Dude, I wasn't calling anyone,
哥们儿 我没给任何人打电话
just playing a video game I already downloaded.
只是在玩我下好了的游戏
Sorry. I guess I'm a little on edge.
对不起 我想我有点儿过于紧张了
Where are we headed anyway, Bulk?
我们这是去哪儿 小隔？
You got some sort of plan?
你有什么计划吗？
We're following standard Wrecker protocol.
我们正按雷霆救援队的标准方案行动
Which is...
方案是…？
An emergency plan we followed during the war
这是我们在大战时制定的紧急计划
in case any Wrecker got standard or separated from the unit.
如果一位雷霆救援队员被困或是掉队
We'd always rendezvous at the exact same set of coordinates.
我们总是会在特定地点会合
If Jack is still alive, he'll be there.
老千肯定还活着 他会去那里的！
Don't stop now.
别停啊
I was just beginning to enjoy myself.
我才刚开始享受呢！
Believe me, Wheeljack,
相信我 千斤顶
there is more where that came from.
还有得你受的！
And you will tell me the location of your compatriots...
我保证你会乖乖告诉我你同伙的藏身之地
... no matter what it takes
用什么手段 花多长时间
... or how long.
我都无所谓…
Like I told you,
不是说了吗
they weren't expecting me.
他们并没有在等我
They never bothered to fill me in.
也根本没告诉我任何信息
So, go ahead.
所以你只管继续
Knock yourself out.
尽管折腾好了…
How may I serve you, Lord Megatron?
威震天陛下 有什么能为您效劳的吗？
Assemble a team and disembark for Cybertron immediately.
集结一支队伍 立刻飞往塞博特恩
While hunting Autobots remains paramount,
以追捕汽车人为首要任务 同时
we must not squander the opportunity to recover any Iacon relics left behind in the chaos.
借此机会 找回在混乱中遗弃在铁堡的遗物
For all we know,
据我们所知
Optimus Prime is out there somewhere
擎天柱正躲在某处
planning to do the same.
谋划着同样的事情…
I-It's okay, Optimus.
没事了 擎天柱
You're with me... Smokescreen.
我就在你身边 我是烟幕
How did... I get here?
我怎么在这里？
When we were evacuating the base, just as the Cons opened fire...
在我们从基地撤离时 也就是虎子开炮那会儿
It was my turn to ground bridge away.
本该轮到我撤离的
But I couldn't do it.
但我做不到
I couldn't let you face Megatron's army alone.
我不能让你独自面对威震天的大军
So, I snuck back.
于是我偷偷溜了回来
But that's when the blast hit,
但基地遭到了攻击
and the whole joint came tumbling down.
已经完全坍塌了
But I managed to pull you from the wreckage before the Cons dove in, using the Phase Shifter,
我设法在虎子来之前利用相位仪把您从废墟中救了出来
which I... managed to snag in all the confusion back on Cybertron.
相位仪是我…在塞博特恩还是一片混乱中抢回来的
I'm... I'm sorry I defied your orders.
呃 很抱歉 我违抗了您的命令…
We're safe here,
我们在这里很安全
but we're down so deep, no one can pick up our signals.
但是我们身处地下 没人能收到我们的信号
I'll have to scout above ground if I'm gonna have any hope of finding Ratchet.
如果我们想找到救护车的话 得去地面
No. No hope.
没…没用的
What do you mean?
什么意思？
The Doc's the only one who can get you patched up.
救护车是唯一能医好你的人！
Optimus.
擎天柱…
What if Jasper wasn't evacuated in time?
如果贾斯帕没有被及时疏散
She could have been hurt
妈妈她可能会受伤
or taken by the Cons.
或者被虎子抓走
Jack...
杰克
And even if she did get out,
就算她逃出来了
she's got to be worried out of her mind not knowing where I am.
没有我的消息 她也肯定急疯了
Jack, calm down.
杰克 冷静点儿
We'll get back to Jasper,
我们会回到贾斯帕的
find a way to reach your mother
想办法找到你妈妈
and the rest of the team.
还有其他队员
Stay here.
留在这儿
Could be a Con on our tail.
可能有虎子跟踪我们
Sorry, mom.
对不起 妈妈
I'd call if I could.
如果情况允许 我一定会打给你的
Oh, one text couldn't hurt, could it?
一条短信应该不会有事吧？
Master.
主人！
Send in the troops.
派出部队
And, Soundwave,
另外 声波
I want a live feed.
为我实时传输现场情况！
Jack.
杰克！
"With Arcee. Safe. Love you."
“我和阿尔茜在一起 很安全 爱你！”
Agent Fowler, Jack's alive!
福勒探员 杰克还活着！
Scrap.
糟了！
Oh... Civilian.
喔 虚惊一场
Jack!
杰克！
I am so toast.
这下我完蛋了！
Smile, Jack.
杰克 笑一个
You're on Decepticon TV.
你上霸天虎电视节目了！
Master. We have a visual.
主人 我们收到画面了
How long does it take to exterminate a lone Autobot and her human pet?!
到底要多久才能干掉一个汽车人和她的人类宠物！
Well, in my experience...
这个嘛 依我的经验…
It's not a riddle, Starscream.
我的话不是疑问句 红蜘蛛！
Sorry.
抱歉…
Over there.
那里！
Not the best cover.
这儿可不是藏身的好地方
We're not here to hide.
我们不是来藏身的…
Hey, guys.
嘿 伙计们
Unleaded or diesel?
加点儿汽油还是柴油啊？
Let's roll before they send reinforcements.
赶在他们派援军到达之前 快撤！
Come on, fellas. Put your backs into it.
伙计们 加把劲 不要偷懒！
The Apex armor.
精锐护甲
Our illustrious leader will be pleased.
我们的伟大领袖会很高兴的
Now, any sign of that Phase Shifter?
仍然没有相位仪的下落吗？
I really liked that thing.
我真心喜欢那东西
Sir.
长官！
By the Allspark.
我的火种源啊…
Well? Did any of the surveillance data survive?
怎么样 还有监控资料留存吗？
Eh... A shame.
唉 可惜了
We might have at least learned the direction in which Arcee and the human fled.
我们本应至少得到阿尔茜和那个人类的逃跑方向…
Clearly, we need to improve our methods of hunting Autobots
显然我们要改进追捕汽车人的方法
and build upon the tactical advantage that we've managed to secure.
并巩固我们已经获得的战术优势
Lord Megatron,
威震天陛下
I am ready to return to Darkmount,
我已准备好返回黑山
and I'm certain you'll want to see what I've uncovered.
而且我敢肯定您看见我的发现后 一定会龙颜大悦的
Soundwave, open a space-bridge portal.
声波 开启太空桥！
I find myself in urgent need of good news,
我现在迫切需要一个好消息
so please, Knockout,
所以 击倒
tell me that you found something useful.
拜托你告诉我 找到了什么有用的宝贝
Some things, my liege.
有一些东西 我的君王
And someone.
还有…某个人！
He... lives?
他还…活着！
Shockwave.
震荡波！
Just the tactical advantage I need.
这正是我所需要的战术优势啊！